iorbix.com 2017-04-10

# Privacy and Terms | iOrbix

Privacy Policy

This agreement was written in English (US).  
Date of Last Revision: August 17, 2015

Please read the Terms of Service and Privacy Policy carefully. By accessing, browsing, using or registering with the iorbix.com website, iOrbix or iOrbix Mobile, you represent and agree that (1) you are at least 13 years of age, (2) you acknowledge that you have read, understood and agree with the Terms of Service, the Privacy Policy and the Cookies and (3) you will comply and be bound by the Terms of Service and the Privacy Policy, including any future modifications.  
If you do not agree to be bound by the Terms of Service or the Privacy Policy in their entirety or you are under 13 years of age, you are not authorized to use the iorbix.com website, iOrbix or iOrbix Mobile. 

What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you fill out a form. When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, e-mail address, sex and birth date. 

What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

**1\. To personalize your experience**  
Your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs.

**2\. To improve our website**  
We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.

**3\. To improve customer service**  
Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.

**4\. To process transactions**  
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested. 

How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you access your personal information. 

Do we use cookies?

Yes, just like many other websites. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your web browser (if you allow that in its settings) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.  
We use cookies to personalise content and ads, to provide social media features and to analyse our traffic. We also share information about your use of our site with our social media, advertising and analytics partners.  
We use cookies to temporarily save your login information for your own convenience.  
We also use cookies for other special features on iOrbix.  
Please read more in our Cookie Policy. 

Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. 

Your account settings and email notifications

When you register on iOrbix, you are automatically subscribed to the email notifications of its basic features.  
However, you may disable some or all notifications via your Account Settings.  
On that page, you can edit your account preferences. You may also delete your account if you no longer wish to share your personal information on iOrbix. 

Profile Visibility

Profiles on iOrbix are set, by default, to be visible by everyone, including people who are not registered on iOrbix.  
This setting can be changed through your Account Settings. You can set your profile visibility to Friends only.  
If your profile visibility is set to Public, everyone will be able to see your public comments, shared messages, blog posts, public photos, gifts and other contents that are not private. 

Sharing Posts on iOrbix

When you share a message (through the Sharing Box from the homepage or your profile), you control the audience, between Public (everyone can see it) or Friends (only people from your Friends List can see it).  
This setting will change its behavior depending on your profile visibility. A post targeting the Public audience will not be visible by everyone if your profile visibility is set to Friends. A post targeting the Friends audience will be visible by people on your Friends List only. If an Album visibility is set to Friends, the visibility of the photo will be to people on your Friends List only. This also means that the post will not appear in the news feed of people who are not on your Friends List. 

Sharing Photos on iOrbix

The visibility of the photos you upload on your profile depend on the Album you post into. If an Album visibility is set to Friends, the visibility of the photo will be to people on your Friends List only. This also means that updates about that photo (upload or comments) will not appear in the news feed of people who are not on your Friends List.  
Always think before you upload a photo. If someone provides the direct link (URL) to a person that is not on your Friends List, that person will be able to see the photo.  
If album visibility is set to Everyone, this setting will change its behavior depending on your profile visibility. This means that if your profile visibility is set to Friends, then the photos in the album will be visible by people on your Friends List only. 

Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites. 

Children

We do not intentionally gather personal information of users and visitors who are under the age of 13. 

Terms and Conditions

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website. 

Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy. 

Changes to our Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to revise our policies at any time without notice.  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. 

Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may email us to our email.

**Disclaimer:** iOrbix and all staff of iOrbix will not be held responsible for (1) any content generated by iOrbix users or (2) content that exists through any links posted on the iOrbix website.

iOrbix and all images associated with iOrbix are © Copyright 2017 iOrbix. All Rights Reserved.
